Werner, Alfred; Papers ger096
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Writings: Articles on Artists, 1903-1979; Undated; 5
  - Kirchner, Ernest Ludwig. Clippings, catalogs, 1950-1969 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 14)
  - Kisling, Moise. Typescripts. Clippings, 1971-1973 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 15)
  - Klee, Paul. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 16)
  - Klee, Paul. Clippings, catalogs, 1955-1974 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 17)
  - klinger, Max. Typescripts, notes, clippings, photographs, catalog, 1970-1971; Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 18)
  - Kokoschka, Oskar. Typescripts, Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 19)
  - Kokoschka, Oskar. Published artcles by Werner, 1959-1976 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 20)
  - Kokoschka, Oskar. Notes, Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 21)
  - Kokoschka, Oskar. Clippings, catalogs in English, 1940-1974 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 22)
  - Kokoschka, Oskar. Clippings, catalogs in German, 1910 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 23)
  - Kollwitz, Kaethe. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 24)
  - kollwitz, kaethe. Clippings, catalogs, 1949-1975 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 25)
  - Kolnik, Arthur. Letter, clippings, 1937-1967; 1L from Kolnik to Werner (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 26)
  - Kopman, Benjamin. Letter, typescripts, notes, clipping, catalogs, 1956-1967; Undated; 1 L. from Kopman to Werner (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 27)
  - Kroll, Leon. Notes, clippings, 1965; Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 28)
  - Kubin, Alfred. Typescripts, notes, clippings, catalogs, 1950-1974; Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 29)
  - L − Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 30)
  - Lasansky, Mauricio. Typescript, clippings, 1967; Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 31)
  - LaTour, Georges. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 32)
  - LaTour, Maurice Quentin de. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 33)
  - Laurencin, Marie. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 34)
  - Lawrence, D.H. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 35)
  - Leger, Fernand. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 36)
  - Lehmbruck, Wilhelm. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 37)
  - Lehmbruck, Wilhelm. Clippings, catalogs, 1963-1964 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 38)
  - Lenko, Sabina. Typescript, Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 39)
  - Levine, Jack. Typescript, clipping, 1970 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 40)
  - Levinger, Nisan. Typescript, Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 41)
  - Levy, Rudolf. Typescript, clippings, 1965; Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 42)
  - Lieberman, Meyer. Typescript, Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 43)
  - Liebermann, Max. Correspondence re: Liebermann; also pc. of 1 L. by Liebermann, 1964-1969 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 44)
  - Liebermann, Max. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1924-1969; Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 45)
  - Liebermann, Max. Notes, Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 16)
  - Liebermann, Max. Artur Gläser:Max Liebermann. Photocopy of typewritten text, Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 17)
  - Lilien, Ephraim Moses. Correspondence re: Lilien, incl. 2 L. from Otto Lilien to Werner. Typescripts, published article, 1958-1976; Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 46)
  - Lilien, Ephraim Moses. Notes, clippings, 1953-1974 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 47)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques. Correspondence re: Lipchitz, 1961 (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 48)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques. Typescripts, Undated (Box 10 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 49-50)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques. Notes, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 1)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques. Student paper, clippings, 1978; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 2)
  - Lismann, Hermann. Typescript, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 3)
  - Liss, Jan. Typescripts, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 4)
  - Lissitzky, El. Typescripts, 1969; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 5)
  - Livni, Zvi. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 6)
  - M − Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 7)
  - Makart, Hans. Typescript, notes, clippings, 1972; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 8)
  - Malka, Yaakov. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 9)
  - Mané-Katz. Typescripts, 1969; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 10)
  - Mané-Katz. Student paper, notes, clippings, 1941-1967 (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 11)
  - Manet, Edouard. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1977; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 12)
  - Mannes, Marya. Notes, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 13)
  - Maranz, Irving. Typescripts, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 14)
  - Marc, Franz. Typescript (review), clippings, 1967; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 15)
  - Marcks, Gerhard, 1967; 1971; 2 L. from Marcks to Werner; copy and translation of 1 L. (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 16)
  - Marcks, Gerhard. Typescripts, notes, clippings, photographs, 1960-1970; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 17)
  - Marin, John. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 18)
  - Marks, Claude. Notes, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 19)
  - Marsh, Reginald. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 20)
  - Mataré, Ewald. Typescript, notes, clippings, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 21)
  - Matisse, Henri. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 22)
  - Matisse, Henri. Clippings, 1953-1974 (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 23)
  - Medzini, Dov. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 24)
  - Meidner, Ludwig. Typescripts, notes, 1969; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 25)
  - Meidner, Ludwig. Clippings, 1963-1966 (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 26)
  - Meier-Graefe, Julius. Typescripts, notes, clipping, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 27)
  - Mendelsohn, Erich. Typescripts, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 28)
  - Menkes, Sigmund. Typescript, notes, clippings, 1942-1969; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 29)
  - Meyer, Franz. Notes, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 30)
  - Meyer de Haan, Joseph. Typescript, notes, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 31)
  - Michelangelo. Typescripts, notes, clipping, photograph, 1963; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 32)
  - Miller, Shulamith W. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 33)
  - Millet, Jean François. Typescript (review), clipping, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 34)
  - Miro. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 35)
  - Modersohn-Becker, Paula [Paula Becker-Modersohn]. Typescript, notes, catalog, clippings, 1960-1968; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 36)
  - Mokady. Typescript, notes, catalog, 1953; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 37)
  - Momiyama, Nanai. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 38)
  - Monet, Claude. Typescript, notes, clippings, 1966; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 39)
  - Monticelli, Adolphe. Typescripts, notes, clippings, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 40)
  - Moore, Henry. Notes, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 41)
  - Morisot, Berthe. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 42)
  - Moses, Grandma. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 43)
  - Mosler, Henry. Notes, clippings, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 44)
  - Mucha, Alphonse. Typescripts (reviews), Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 45)
  - Münter, Gabriele. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1961-1970; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 46)
  - Myers, Myer. Typescripts, notes, clippings, catalog, photograph, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 47)
  - N − Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 48)
  - Naaman, Miriam. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 49)
  - Nadelman, Elie. Typescripts, published article, notes, clippings, catalogs, 1948-1975 (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 50)
  - Nemes, Veronika. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 51)
  - Nemeth, Lajos. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 52)
  - Neumann, Anna. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 53)
  - Neumann, Barnett. Typescript, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 54)
  - Nolde, Emil. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 55)
  - Nolde, Emil. Clippings, catalogs, photographs, 1955-1973 (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 56)
  - O − Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 57)
  - O'Keefe, Georgia. Typescripts (reviews), clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 58)
  - Oppenheim, Moritz. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 59)
  - Oppenheim, Moritz. Clippings, catalogs, 1956-1974; Undated (Box 11 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 60)
  - Opper, Frederick Burr. Notes, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 1)
  - Orlik, Emil. Typescript, notes, 1970; Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 2)
  - Orloff, Chana. Typescript, notes, catalog, clippings, 1926-1970; Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 3)
  - Orozco, José. Typescripts, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 4)
  - Osthaus, Karl Ernst. Typescript, photographs, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 5)
  - Owen, Peter. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 6)
  - P − Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 7)
  - Pacher, Michael. Typescript, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 8)
  - Pankok, Otto. Letters, clippings, 1966-1972; 2 L. from Hulda Pankok to Werner (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 9)
  - Pevsner, Anton. Typescript, clipping, 1970; Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 10)
  - Picart, Bernard. Notes, clipping, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 11)
  - Picasso, Pablo. Typescripts, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 12)
  - Picasso, Pablo. Notes, photographs, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 13)
  - Picasso, Pablo. Clippings, 1953-1974 (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 14)
  - Pilichowski, Leopold. Typescript, 1969 (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 15)
  - Piranesi. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 16)
  - Pisanello. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 17)
  - Pissarro, Camille. Correspondence re: research on Pissarro, 1953-1965 (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 18)
  - Pissarro, Camille. Typescripts, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 19)
  - Pissarro, Camille. Notes, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 20)
  - Pissarro, Camille. Student papers, postcards, 1974 (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 21)
  - Pissarro, Camille. Clippings, catalogs, 1944-1978 (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 22)
  - Plowitz, Kurt. Typescript, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 23)
  - Pompon, François. Typescript, notes, clippings, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 24)
  - Pontormo, Jacopa da. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 25)
  - Popper-Lynkeus, Josef. Typescript, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 26)
  - R − Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 27)
  - Raphael. Typescripts, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 28)
  - Raskin, Saul. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 29)
  - Rattner, Abraham. Typescripts, notes, clippings, catalogs, 1935-1978; Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 30)
  - Reder, Bernard. Typescript, clippings, catalogs, 1961-1968; Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 31)
  - Rembrandt. Texts of lectures given by Werner in Detroit and Chicago, typescripts, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 32-33)
  - Rembrandt. Typescripts, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 34-35)
  - Rembrandt. Typescripts (reviews), Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 36)
  - Rembrandt. Copies of published articles by Werner, 1957-1974 (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 37)
  - Rembrandt. Notes, Undated (Box 12 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 38-40)
  - Rembrandt. Student Papers, clippings, in English, 1906-1978 (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 1-2)
  - Rembrandt. Clippings, in German, 1964-1969 (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 3)
  - Rembrandt. Photographs reproductins of art work, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 4-5)
  - Rembrandt. Photographs reproductins of art work, Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 18)
  - Remington, Frederick. Typescripts (reviews), Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 6)
  - Renoir, Pierre-Auguste. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1971-1974; Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 7)
  - Reynolds, Sir Joshua. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 8)
  - Rhodes, Anthony. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 9)
  - Reimenshneider, Tilman. Typescripts, photographs, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 10)
  - Reimenshneider, Tilman. Notes, Clippings, 1962-1965 (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 11)
  - Rilke, Rainer Maria. Typescript, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 12)
  - Rivera, Diego. Typescipts, notes, clippings, 1957; Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 13)
  - Rodan, Yehuda Typescript, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 14)
  - Rodin, Auguste. Typescipts, notes, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 15)
  - Rohr, Joel. Typescripts, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 16)
  - Romako, Anton. Typescipts, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 17)
  - Romano. Emanuel. Typescripts, clippings, 1940-1968; Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 18)
  - Rops, Felicien. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1967; Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 19)
  - Rosenberger, Edith. Typescipt, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 20)
  - Rosenthal, Bernard, 1955; 1 L. From Hailia Rosenthal to Werner (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 21)
  - Rosenthal, Max. Typescript, notes, 1970 (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 22)
  - Rosenthal, Seymour, Undated; 1 card from Rosenthal to Werner (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 23)
  - Roth, Lior. Typescript, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 24)
  - Rothbort, Samuel. Typescript, clippings, 1954; Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 25)
  - Rothstein, Irma. Typescript, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 26)
  - Rousseau, Henri. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 27)
  - Rousseau, Henri. Clippings, 1925-1974 (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 28)
  - Rowlandson, Thomas. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 29)
  - Rubens, Peter Paul. Typescripts (review), Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 30)
  - Rubin, Rueven, 1973-1974; 2 L., 1 card from Esther Rubin to Werner (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 31)
  - Ryback, Issachar. Typescripts, notes, clippings, catalogs, 1923-1975 (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 32)
  - Ryback, Issachar. Reproductions of artwork, Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 19)
  - S- Artists. Clippings on artist, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 33)
  - Salomon, Charlotte. Typescripts, 1970; Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 34)
  - Satt, Berel. Typescipt, notes, catalog, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 35)
  - Schahames, Samson. Typescript, notes, catalogs, 1959; Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 36)
  - Schatz, Boris, Published article by Werner, notes, clippings, 1942-1971 (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 37)
  - Scherer, Michael. Typescript, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 38)
  - Schiele, Egon. Typescript, published article by Werner, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 39)
  - Schiele, Egon. Notes, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 40)
  - Schiele, Egon. Clippings, catalogs, 1957-1975 (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 41)
  - Schloss, Ezekiel. Typescript, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 42)
  - Schnitzler, Arthur. Typescripts, published articles by Werner, 1942-1971 (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 43)
  - Schor, Ilya. Typescipts, Undated (Box 13 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 44)
  - Segall, Lasar. Typescripts, notes clippings, 1953-1970 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 1)
  - Shahn, Ben, 1973; Undated; 1 L. from Ben Shahn to Werner; 2 cards from Bernarda Shahn to Werner (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 2)
  - Shahn, Ben. Typescripts, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 3)
  - Schan, Ben. Notes, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 4)
  - Shahn, Ben. Clippings, catalogs, 1947-1977 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 5)
  - Schalom of Safred. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1966-1972 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 6)
  - Scecter, Mark Henry. Typescript, reprints of article by Werner, clippings, 1975-1979 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 7)
  - Sheeler, Charles. Typescript, clipping, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 8)
  - Sherman, Sarai. Typescript, notes, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 9)
  - Signac, Paul. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 10)
  - Sisley, Alfred. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 11)
  - Sloan, John. Typescripts, clipping, 1955; Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 12)
  - Soloman, Simeon. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 13)
  - Solomon, Simeon. Clippings, catalogs, 1951-1971 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 14)
  - Sorolla y Batista, Joaquin. Typescript, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 15)
  - Soyer, Ralphael and Issac. Typescripts, clippings, catalogs, 1953-1973 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 16)
  - Speer, Albert. Transcripts, letter, photograph, 1970-1971; PC of Speer L. (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 17)
  - Sroczynski, Leon. Typescripts, 1976; Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 18)
  - Stein, Gertrude, Miichael and Leo. Typescipts, photographs, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 19)
  - Steinhardt, Jakob, 1966-1967; 3 L. from Minni Steinhardt to Werner (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 20)
  - Steinhardt, Jakob. Typescripts, printed articles by Werner, 1968-1973 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 21)
  - Steinhardt, Jakob. Notes, clippings, catalogs, 1939-1968 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 22)
  - Stenhal [Henri Boyle]. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 23)
  - Sterne, Maurice. Typescript (review) notes, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 24)
  - Stillman, Ary. Transcripts, notes, catalog, clippings, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 25)
  - Struck, Hermann. Transcripts, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 26)
  - Stuck, Franz von. Notes, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 27)
  - Szyk, Authur. Typescript, clippings, 1929-1969 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 28)
  - T- Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 29)
  - Tauber, Blanka. Typescipt, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 30)
  - Teichmann, Sabia. Typescript, text of an interview, notes, 1968; Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 31)
  - Ticho, Anna. Letters, portrait photography, Undated; 3 L. from Ticho to Werner (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 32)
  - Ticho, Anna. Typescripts, notes, catalogs, clippings, 1930-1974 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 33)
  - Tofel, Jennings. Typescripts, notes, catalogs, clippings, 1928-1959 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 34)
  - Toffoli, Louis. Typescripts, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 35)
  - Toron, Paul. Typescript, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 36)
  - Touslouse-Lautrec, Henri. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 37)
  - Towne, Francis. Typescripts (review), Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 38)